export const data = [
  {
    id: "0",
    correctAnswer: "KONO DIO DA",
    answers: ["Dio", "ZA WARUDO", "No one", "KONO DIO DA"],
    question: "You thought it was ------ , but in reality , ¿Who was it?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    id: "1",
    correctAnswer: "Tokyo Revengers",
    answers: ["Haikyuu", "Slam dunk", "Hajime no ippo", "Tokyo Revengers"],
    question: "¿Which of this anime is not a Spokon?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    correctAnswer: "Evangelion",
    answers: ["Detective Conan", "One piece", "Evangelion", "Cowboy Bebop"],
    question: "¿Which anime came first?",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    correctAnswer: "Soredemo Sekai wa Utsukushii",
    answers: ["Soredemo Sekai wa Utsukushii", "Rainy Days", "Kamisama Hajimemashita", "A silent Voice"],
    question: "¿Which of this anime has, 'Tender Rain', as it main song?",
    difficulty: "extra-hard",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    correctAnswer: "s1mple",
    answers: ["dev1ce", "coldzera", "baldu", "s1mple"],
    question: "¿Who is considered the best player of the decade?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    correctAnswer: "Astralis",
    answers: ["NIP", "FNC", "Astralis", "9z"],
    question: "¿Who has the most major titles?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    correctAnswer: "G2",
    answers: ["G2", "G2", "G2", "G2"],
    question: "¿Which team chokes the most?",
    difficulty: "extra-hard",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    correctAnswer: "VIP/Outsiders",
    answers: ["G2(they choke in RMR)", "Na'Vi", "VIP/Outsiders", "Heroic"],
    question: "¿Who was the last major winner (November of 2022)?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    correctAnswer: "TenZ",
    answers: ["TenZ", "kennyS", "mONESY", "DvK1ng.-"],
    question: "¿Which proplayer is obsessed with anime?",
    difficulty: "medium",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    correctAnswer: "wtf, I don't care, I do the questions and answers, f#ck you",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "Kinda", "wtf, I don't care, I do the questions and answers, f#ck you"],
    question: "¿Was it weird to mix CSGO with Anime?",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
];
